+91 9972321347



vidhya4ever@gmail.com



1/119 Shanthimedu, CBE - 641019



VIDHYALAKSHMI

VENKATESH

Engineering Project Lead- QA

CAREER OBJECTIVE

Dedicated Software tester with more than 12 years of experience in manual testing environment and recent experience in automation. Easily collaborate with developers to accomplish the milestones. Excellent analysis, evaluation, and a strong attention to small details for accurately identifying the problems and bugs.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ENGINEERING PROJECT LEAD -QUALITY ASSURANCE

Aosta India Pvt. Ltd., / Coimbatore / 2020 - Present

- Involved END to END workflow of patient in HMS including Functional and Administrative Modules.
- Developed test suite using **ROBOT FRAMEWORK** for regression workflows.
- Establish MS SQL server connectivity to retrieve the test data from backend using selenium.

ASSOCIATE CONSULTANT

Siemens Healthcare Pvt. Ltd., / Bangalore / 2010 – 2016

- Preparing and reviewing test reports for various test cycles.
- Trained for Real Lab Clinical Workflows of Angiography applications at Chicago, USA.
- Act as an internal auditor to maintain and review all the quality related documents like Review checklist, Test reports, Environment checklist.
- Worked with QAliber and Auto IT automation Tool to perform Exploratory Testing and Regression Testing.

PROGRAMMER ANALYST

Cognizant Technology & Services Pvt. Ltd., / Chennai / 2006 - 2010

- Prepared Test and Evaluation strategy, Test scenarios, Test Cases and also involved in preparing the Test Data for Test Execution.
- Preparing and sending the testing status reports to clients on daily basis.
- Prepared Test and Evaluation strategy, Test scenarios, Test Cases and also involved in preparing the Test Data for Test Execution.

EDUCATION

Masters / Computer Science University Of Madras, Chennai 2010

> BSc / Electronics PSG CAS , Coimbatore 2006

KEY SKILLS

Analytical thinking, planning

Strong communication

Tolerant and flexible

Organization and prioritization

AWARDS

SPOT AWARD / 2015 / SIEMENS

STAR OF THE YEAR / 2009 / COGNIZANT

TOOLS

TEST AUTOMATION TOOL – Eclipse IDE(Python 2.7 Ver, Pycharm(Python 3.12 Ver)

TEST MANAGEMENT TOOL – Quality Center, Rally, Microsoft TFS

XML TOOL - SOAP UI, UBMATRIX